# **ROBERT SMITH**

### **Sr.Senior Tester**

Phone: (0123)-456-789 | Email: info@qwikresume.com | Website: Qwikresume.com

#### SUMMARY

Over 7+ years of total IT experience Software Design, Development, Testing with emphasis Quality Assurance. Proficient both Manual Testing. Expertise System Requirement Analysis, GUI Testing, functionality testing, Integration Testing, Stress/Load testing, Black box techniques, Regression Testing, Security testing, User Acceptance testing, Compatibility testing, Integration testing, Smoke testing System testing.

#### **CORE COMPETENCIES**

Mainframe, SQL, Functional, Manual, UAT, CBT Testing, In Baking and Home Loan Mortgage domain.

#### PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

#### **Sr.Senior Tester**

ABC Corporation - July 2009 - October 2011

#### **Key Deliverables:**

- Project Cluster Availability Application Tru64 UNIX Group delivers very matured and stable operating system.
- Tru64 UNIX provides symmetric multiprocessing (SMP), real-time support, numerous features to assist application programmers in developing applications that use shared libraries, multithread support, memory-mapped files.
- TruCluster software was used for cluster based installation and operations.
- Tru64 UNIX offered clustering facility named TruCluster Server.
- TruCluster utilised cluster-wide filesystem visible to each cluster member, plus member specific storage.
- Accountable for all necessary OS installations.
- Woked on agile methodology.

#### Sr.Senior Tester

Delta Corporation - 2006 - 2009

#### **Key Deliverables:**

- Tested individual tubes for visual and electrical defects and made adjustments if necessary.
- Learned to test and make adjustments to a variety of tubes " Have undergone a National Agency Check with Local Agency Check (NACLC) background.
- Government classified information at the Secret level on 11/07/07 (issuing agency DISCO).
- Period 18 Oct 2014 Till Date Project Description To assess the upgraded Selling and Definition System and assessment engine also assessment of.
- Roles and Responsibilities- Thorough understanding of requirement for allocated SRSs Write/verify/review test cases accuracy and test case count.

# **ROBERT SMITH**

## **Sr.Senior Tester**

Phone: (0123)-456-789 | Email: info@qwikresume.com | Website: Qwikresume.com

- Assigned as Senior Tester at the Maryland State Board of Elections voting system upgrade.
- This is an electronic voting system that uses a touch screen voting ballot.

#### **EDUCATION**

B.Tech In Mechanical Engineering - (SASTRA University - Thanjavur, Tamil Nadu)